http://www.tesh.com/privacy

About UsPodcastConcert DatesPBS ListingsFind the ShowGet the NewsletterSearchHealthLoveMoneyPetsSleepWorkplaceOnline StoreSearch ResultsSorry about that, no articles matching
'' were found.Privacy PolicyOur Privacy PolicyRespecting the privacy and the security of your personal information is important to us. We realize that providing us with personal information is an act of trust. Therefore, we have created a Privacy Policy to show you the steps we have taken to secure that trust. Please take a few moments to read this privacy policy carefully.Collected InformationThere are certain instances where you may be asked to provide your personal information on our site. The information that we collect is for administrative use only. We use it to better understand and serve your needs, as well as provide you with services that may be uniquely valuable to you. Our site is designed to provide information to you that is relevant to the profile you have provided to us.Use of InformationWe do not use the information you provide us for any purpose unless otherwise consented by you personally. Information submitted will not be available to anyone other than our staff or business partners whose services you have requested. This information is specifically used by our partners to provide you with the services you have requested and is not redistributed in any way.We make every effort to keep our listeners and supporters informed of special events, news, and offers that are happening or available. Periodically, announcements are released via email or by direct mail. If you do not wish to be contacted, simply respond to the email or visit our website and complete the unsubscribe form found at the bottom of the page.Note: Your information will be subjected to submission if ordered by a court of law.SecurityWe are determined to keep your information private. We have even added measures to protect your personal information in transitions. For example, when you supply us with your debit card or checking account information to make a purchase, your information is encrypted to insure a safe and secure transaction. Your payment information is temporarily stored on a secure server before processing. All of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access through (1) the use of vendors that specialize in providing secure online payment solutions and by (2) not allowing your account/payment information to be accessed via the internet.ContactPlease contact us if you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy. You are welcome to call our Customer Care Center at 1-877-801-4995 between 8:30 a.m. and 5:30 p.m. PST to speak with a customer service representative.You may also contact us by e-mail at customer_service@teshmedia.comGarden City Music
PO Box 6010-721
Sherman Oaks, CA 91413HealthLoveMoneyPetsSleepWorkplaceAll ArticlesSubmit VideoNewsletterFAQAbout UsPrivacy PolicyContact UsAdvertise© Tesh.com 2020Subscribe to our newsletterJohn's weekly newsletterSubscribeOrder the Book×Sign up for the Weekly Top StoriesFirst Name *Last NameEmail * ZipcodeFields marked with * are required.Weekly Top StoriesIntelligence For Your Pets NewsletterKeep Me Updated On Concert NewsSubscribe×John Tesh - RelentlessOrder John's new book: “RELENTLESS: Unleashing A Life Of Purpose, Grit and Faith” NOW - Hardcover & Audiobook available!
Order now!
